<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>WPI Esports</title>
    <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WPI Esports</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://wpiesports.github.io/logo.png</url>
      <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/logo.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://wpiesports.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Events</title>
      <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 13:06:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wpiesports.github.io/events/</guid>
      <description>September 29, 12:00pm League of Legends Tournament Our first tournament of the year will be for League of Legends, on Sunday, September 29th, starting 12pm. All games will take place in the East Hall Esports Lab. Any WPI student is welcome to play regardless of being a &amp;ldquo;member&amp;rdquo; of WPI esports, so invite your friends and sign up! Please make sure if you&amp;rsquo;re signing up with a team please make sure all team members fill out the form and put the EXACT SAME TEAMMATES.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:06:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wpiesports.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Esports at WPI WPI has been competing in esports for over 6 years in a wide range of titles. We currently support 11 games with over 150 members participating on teams. We also find opportunities for members to get involved in other areas of esports like broadcasting, coaching, or managing teams. We&amp;rsquo;re always looking to build on our teams and the opportunities we provide to WPI students.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like to contact us, join our Discord or send an email to gr-esports-exec@wpi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Esports Lab</title>
      <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/esports_lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:06:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wpiesports.github.io/esports_lab/</guid>
      <description>About The Esports Lab has 12 fully equipped PCs open for members of the WPI community to use for events and gaming.
Specifications &amp;amp; Software Each computer is preloaded with the same software and has a set of peripherals for use. If you&amp;rsquo;d like, you can download your own software and games for use on the PC. You can also bring peripherals to plug into USB hubs on the tables. A full list of specifications, peripherals, and software found on the PCs can be found here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff</title>
      <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:06:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wpiesports.github.io/staff/</guid>
      <description>Club Executives          President Josh K. (Kesstrel)   Vice President Yara N. (soapsugie)   Secretary Jon T. (SwiftPanda)   Treasurer Vijay M. (Schnellaffe)   Event Manager Irene (ZeraRin)    Contact us in our discord or send an email to gr-esports-exec@wpi.edu!
Specialized Admins          Caster Daniel (Jraxen)   Event Coordinator Andrea M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teams</title>
      <link>https://wpiesports.github.io/teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:06:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wpiesports.github.io/teams/</guid>
      <description>Counter-Strike 2 League of Legends Signups for League of Legends 2024 are open: signup form
osu! Overwatch 2 Rocket League Splatoon Signups for Splatoon 2024 are open: signup form
Founded in the Fall of 2022, WPI Splatoon Folks has grown into a sizable program with members across various competitive levels. Primarily focused on competition within the Collegiate Cephalopod Association (CCA), WPI teams have a rich competitive history and serve as one of the cornerstones of the collegiate community.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
